bellybelly.com.au 2014-02-09

# BellyBelly Privacy Policy

  * Conception »
  * Pregnancy »
  * Birth »
  * Breastfeeding »
  * Parenting »
  * Health & Lifestyle »
  * Recipes & Cooking »
  * Advertise »

Pregnancy Week (Select): |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |   |    
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  

---|---  
  
## Privacy Policy for BellyBelly Website Visitors

Bellybelly realises that privacy is a very important matter to our visitors and members. For this reason, we will always strive to protect your privacy as best we can. Below are ways in which information is collected, and what happens to that information.

### Automatic logging of website traffic

Bellybelly keeps a log of web traffic to the site, which is very common practice with most websites. This information logged does not contain any personal details such as the name or address of the visitor. It is only used for general purposes, such as finding out which other sites visitors are coming from, and which pages they visit on BellyBelly.

### Cookies

BellyBelly uses cookies, for example in sections of the site where you log on or place a vote on any of our polls. This enables the website to Ôremember thingsÕ for example, to keep track of whether a visitor has already voted for particular questions. There is no other use of cookies at this site and cookies are not used in any way to collect personal data of visitors.

### Advertisers

Advertiser links and/or banners on the BellyBelly website may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our website as mentioned above, any cookies received with banner ads are collected by the advertiser, and we do not have access to this information. Bellybelly.com.au is selective in which advertisers we allow to advertise on our site; however BellyBelly is not responsible in any way for content found on these sites or the information provided within them.

### External Links

The BellyBelly website contains links to other sites. Bellybelly.com.au is not responsible in any way for content found on these sites, the information provided within them or their privacy practices.

### Public Discussions and Forums

BellyBelly offers open discussions and forums to take place on our website for its members. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Please be sure to read the Forum Guidelines for more information.

### Platinum Membership

Platinum Members of BellyBelly will be required to submit their personal details when signing up. This information is not publicly viewable or accessible, and it is not shared with any third parties. Bellybelly.com.au does not and will not sell nor distribute its members information at any time to any marketing companies.

### Security

Bellybelly.com.au has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of personal information under our control. This information is hidden and secured from the public and is not shared with third parties, with the exception of website developers and the website hosting company who may need to access it to resolve any errors should they occur.

### Children

The BellyBelly website does not contain any pornographic or violent material. We also strive to ensure that the sites we link to and represent meet the same standards, with the exception of adultshop.com.au, who provide information on products suitable for couples of a ÔsoftÕ nature. However, the adult nature of some of the topics related to pre-conception to parenthood mean that some of the information in this site and the sites that we link to may be unsuitable for children. Parents should supervise their children’s internet use in general and for certain sections of this site in particular. Further, we can not be held responsible for all the content at the sites that we link to, especially if it changes after we add our link. This site does not purposefully collect personal data on children (or adults) in any way except as defined above.

### Contacting BellyBelly

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us at [info@bellybelly.com.au](mailto:info@bellybelly.com.au).
